export const acronyms = [
  { front: "<b>ACARS</b>", back: "<b>A</b>ircraft <b>C</b>ommunications, <b>A</b>ddressing, and <b>R</b>eporting <b>S</b>ystem<br>(Text based)" },
  { front: "<b>AC PACK</b>", back: "<b>A</b>ir <b>C</b>ycling and <b>P</b>ressurization, <b>A</b>ir <b>C</b>onditioning <b>K</b>it" },
  { front: "<b>ADF</b>", back: "<b>A</b>utomatic <b>D</b>irection <b>F</b>inder" },
  { front: "<b>ADS-B</b>", back: "<b>A</b>utomatic <b>D</b>ependent <b>S</b>urveillance-<b>B</b>roadcast<br>(Mode C Required)" },
  { front: "<b>AIRMET</b>", back: "<b>Air</b>man's <b>Met</b>eorological Information" },
  { front: "<b>ALD</b>", back: "<b>A</b>vailable <b>L</b>anding <b>D</b>istance" },
  { front: "<b>ALS</b>", back: "<b>A</b>pproach <b>L</b>ighting <b>S</b>ystem" },
  { front: "<b>AFM</b>", back: "<b>A</b>ircraft <b>F</b>light <b>M</b>anual" },
  { front: "<b>APU</b>", back: "<b>A</b>uxiliary <b>P</b>ower <b>U</b>nit<br>(Eletrical and Pneumatic)" },
  { front: "<b>APV</b>", back: "<b>A</b>pproach <b>P</b>rocedure with <b>V</b>ertical Guidance" },
  { front: "<b>ANP</b>", back: "<b>A</b>ctual <b>N</b>avigation <b>P</b>erformance" },
  { front: "<b>ANU</b>", back: "<b>A</b>ircraft <b>N</b>ose <b>U</b>p" },
  { front: "<b>AOA</b>", back: "<b>A</b>ngle <b>o</b>f <b>A</b>ttack" },
  { front: "<b>ARP</b>", back: "<b>A</b>irport <b>R</b>eference <b>P</b>oint" },
  { front: "<b>ARINC</b>", back: "<b>Air</b> Nautical <b>Inc</b>orporated" },
  { front: "<b>ASDA</b>", back: "<b>A</b>ccelerate <b>S</b>top <b>D</b>istance <b>A</b>vailable" },
  { front: "<b>ASI</b>", back: "<b>A</b>ir<b>s</b>peed <b>I</b>ndicator" },
  { front: "<b>ASOS</b>", back: "<b>A</b>utomated <b>S</b>urface <b>O</b>bserving <b>S</b>ystem" },
  { front: "<b>ATC</b>", back: "<b>A</b>ir <b>T</b>raffic <b>C</b>ontrol" },
  { front: "<b>ATCC</b>", back: "<b>A</b>ir <b>T</b>raffic <b>C</b>ontrol <b>C</b>enter" },
  { front: "<b>ATCSCC</b>", back: "<b>A</b>ir <b>T</b>raffic <b>C</b>ontrol <b>S</b>ystem <b>C</b>ommand <b>C</b>enter" },
  { front: "<b>ATCT</b>", back: "<b>A</b>ir <b>T</b>raffic <b>C</b>ontrol <b>T</b>ower" },
  { front: "<b>ARTCC</b>", back: "<b>A</b>ir <b>R</b>oute <b>T</b>raffic <b>C</b>ommand <b>C</b>enter" },
  { front: "<b>ATIS</b>", back: "<b>A</b>utomated <b>T</b>erminal <b>I</b>nformation <b>S</b>ervice<br>(D for Digital)" },
  { front: "<b>ATP</b>", back: "<b>A</b>irline <b>T</b>ransport <b>P</b>ilot Certification" },
  { front: "<b>AWOS</b>", back: "<b>A</b>utomated <b>W</b>eather <b>O</b>bserving <b>S</b>ystem" },
  { front: "<b>BOW</b>", back: "<b>B</b>asic <b>O</b>perating <b>W</b>eight<br>(Airplane + Crew; no fuel/payload)" },
  { front: "<b>CASS</b>", back: "<b>C</b>ockpit <b>A</b>ccess <b>S</b>ecurity <b>S</b>ystem" },
  { front: "<b>CAVOK</b>", back: "<b>C</b>eiling <b>a</b>nd <b>V</b>isibility <b>OK</b>" },
  { front: "<b>CDL</b>", back: "<b>C</b>onfiguration <b>D</b>eviation <b>L</b>ist" },
  { front: "<b>CFR</b>", back: "<b>C</b>ode of <b>F</b>ederal <b>R</b>egulations" },
  { front: "<b>CL</b>", back: "<b>C</b>enterline <b>L</b>ights" },
  { front: "<b>CLM</b>", back: "<b>C</b>enterline <b>M</b>arkings" },
  { front: "<b>CVR</b>", back: "<b>C</b>ockpit <b>V</b>oice <b>R</b>ecorder" },
  { front: "<b>DCT</b>", back: "<b>D</b>irect" },
  { front: "<b>DA</b>", back: "<b>D</b>ecision <b>A</b>ltitude" },
  { front: "<b>DME</b>", back: "<b>D</b>istance <b>M</b>easuring <b>E</b>quipment" },
  { front: "<b>DX</b>", back: "<b>D</b>ispatch" },
  { front: "<b>EAR</b>", back: "<b>E</b>levator, <b>A</b>ilerons, <b>R</b>udder" },
  { front: "<b>EFIS</b>", back: "<b>E</b>lectronic <b>F</b>light <b>I</b>nstrument <b>S</b>ystem" },
  { front: "<b>ELT</b>", back: "<b>E</b>mergency <b>L</b>ocator <b>T</b>ransmitter" },
  { front: "<b>EPR</b>", back: "<b>E</b>ngine <b>P</b>ressure <b>R</b>atio" },
  { front: "<b>ETOPS</b>", back: "<b>Ext</b>ended <b>Op</b>erations" },
  { front: "<b>ETP</b>", back: "<b>E</b>xtended <b>T</b>ime <b>P</b>oints" },
  { front: "<b>FAF</b>", back: "<b>F</b>inal <b>A</b>pproach <b>F</b>ix" },
  { front: "<b>FAP</b>", back: "<b>F</b>inal <b>A</b>pproach <b>P</b>oint" },
  { front: "<b>FAR</b>", back: "<b>F</b>ederal <b>A</b>viation <b>R</b>egulations" },
  { front: "<b>FATWIVES</b>", back: "<ul><li><b>F</b>uel</li><li><b>A</b>irports</li><li><b>T</b>rip/<b>T</b>ail#</li><li><b>W</b>eather</li><li><b>I</b>FR</li><li><b>V</b>FR</li><li><b>E</b>TOPS/<b>E</b>TP</li><li><b>S</b>ignatures</li></ul>" },
  { front: "<b>FD</b>", back: "<b>F</b>light <b>D</b>irector" },
  { front: "<b>FMC</b>", back: "<b>F</b>light <b>M</b>anagement <b>C</b>omputer" },
  { front: "<b>FMS</b>", back: "<b>F</b>light <b>M</b>anagement <b>S</b>ystem" },
  { front: "<b>FOD</b>", back: "<b>F</b>oreign <b>O</b>bject <b>D</b>ebris<br><b>F</b>oreign <b>O</b>bject <b>D</b>amage" },
  { front: "<b>GLAM</b>", back: "<b>G</b>lideslope, <b>L</b>ocalizer, <b>A</b>pproach Lights, <b>M</b>arker Beacons" },
  { front: "<b>GNSS</b>", back: "<b>G</b>lobal <b>N</b>avigation <b>s</b>atellite <b>S</b>ystem" },
  { front: "<b>GPS</b>", back: "<b>G</b>lobal <b>P</b>osition <b>S</b>ystem<br>(Triangulation)" },
  { front: "<b>GPWS</b>", back: "<b>G</b>round <b>P</b>roximity <b>W</b>arning <b>S</b>ystem" },
  { front: "<b>GS</b>", back: "<b>G</b>lide <b>S</b>lope" },
  { front: "<b>HAT</b>", back: "<b>H</b>eight <b>A</b>bove <b>T</b>ouchdown" },
  { front: "<b>HSI</b>", back: "<b>H</b>orizontal <b>S</b>ituation <b>I</b>ndicator" },
  { front: "<b>HUD</b>", back: "<b>H</b>eads <b>U</b>p <b>D</b>isplay" },
  { front: "<b>IAF</b>", back: "<b>I</b>nitial <b>A</b>pproach <b>F</b>ix" },
  { front: "<b>IAP</b>", back: "<b>I</b>nstrument <b>A</b>pproach <b>P</b>late" },
  { front: "<b>IF</b>", back: "<b>I</b>ntermediate <b>F</b>ix" },
  { front: "<b>IFR</b>", back: "<b>I</b>nstrument <b>F</b>light <b>R</b>ules" },
  { front: "<b>ILS</b>", back: "<b>I</b>nstrument <b>L</b>anding <b>S</b>ystem (GLAM)" },
  { front: "<b>IM</b>", back: "<b>I</b>nner <b>M</b>arker" },
  { front: "<b>INS</b>", back: "<b>I</b>nertial <b>N</b>avigation <b>S</b>ystem<br>(Gyroscopes, Accelerometers)" },
  { front: "<b>INT</b>", back: "<b>Int</b>erceptor" },
  { front: "<b>INT</b>", back: "<b>Int</b>ercom" },
  { front: "<b>ISA</b>", back: "<b>I</b>nternational <b>S</b>tandard <b>A</b>tmosphere" },
  { front: "<b>JROUTE</b>", back: "<b>J</b>uliett <b>Rotue</b> - High Altitude Route Connected with VORs" },
  { front: "<b>LDA</b>", back: "<b>L</b>anding <b>D</b>istance <b>A</b>vailable" },
  { front: "<b>LeMAC</b>", back: "<b>L</b>eading <b>E</b>dge <b>M</b>ean <b>A</b>erodynamic <b>C</b>hord" },
  { front: "<b>LLWS</b>", back: "<b>L</b>ow <b>L</b>evel <b>W</b>ind <b>S</b>hear" },
  { front: "<b>LOC</b>", back: "<b>Loc</b>alizer (4 Letters IABC)" },
  { front: "<b>LOM</b>", back: "<b>L</b>ocator <b>O</b>uter <b>M</b>arker" },
  { front: "<b>LIM</b>", back: "<b>L</b>ocator <b>I</b>nner <b>M</b>aker" },
  { front: "<b>LMM</b>", back: "<b>L</b>ocator <b>M</b>iddle <b>M</b>arker" },
  { front: "<b>LPV</b>", back: "<b>L</b>ocalizer <b>P</b>erformance with <b>V</b>ertical Guidance" },
  { front: "<b>MAC</b>", back: "<b>M</b>ean <b>A</b>erodynamic <b>C</b>hord<br>(W&B)" },
  { front: "<b>MAA</b>", back: "<b>M</b>aximum <b>A</b>uthorized <b>A</b>ltitude<br>(Prevents Nav Aid Interference)" },
  { front: "<b>MAHF</b>", back: "<b>M</b>issed <b>A</b>pproach <b>H</b>olding <b>F</b>ix" },
  { front: "<b>MALS</b>", back: "<b>M</b>edium Intensity <b>A</b>pproach <b>L</b>ight <b>S</b>ystem" },
  { front: "<b>MALSF</b>", back: "<b>M</b>edium Intensity <b>A</b>pproach <b>L</b>ight System With <b>S</b>equenced <b>F</b>lashing Lights" },
  { front: "<b>MALSR</b>", back: "<b>M</b>edium Intensity <b>A</b>pproach <b>L</b>ighting <b>S</b>ystem with <b>R</b>AIL" },
  { front: "<b>MAP</b>", back: "<b>M</b>issed <b>A</b>pproach <b>P</b>oint" },
  { front: "<b>MCA</b>", back: "<b>M</b>inimum <b>C</b>rossing <b>A</b>ltitude" },
  { front: "<b>MC</b>", back: "<b>M</b>agnetic <b>C</b>ourse" },
  { front: "<b>MDA</b>", back: "<b>M</b>inimum <b>D</b>escent <b>A</b>ltitude" },
  { front: "<b>MEA</b>", back: "<b>M</b>inimum <b>E</b>nroute <b>A</b>ltitude" },
  { front: "<b>MEL</b>", back: "<b>M</b>inimum <b>E</b>quipment <b>L</b>ist" },
  { front: "<b>METAR</b>", back: "<b>M</b><b>e</b><b>t</b>eorological <b>A</b>erodrome <b>R</b>eport" },
  { front: "Drift Down: <b>Method 1</b>", back: "At the point of engine failure, you drift down and maintain 1000’ clearance over critical obstacles<br>(Mostly Mountain Peaks)" },
  { front: "Drift Down: <b>Method 2</b>", back: "At the point of engine failure, you drift down clearing a critical obstacle by 1000’ and drift down into a valley requiring a drift down alternate" },
  { front: "<b>MLGW</b>", back: "<b>M</b>aximum <b>L</b>anding <b>G</b>ross <b>W</b>eight" },
  { front: "<b>MOA</b>", back: "<b>M</b>ilitary <b>O</b>peration <b>A</b>rea" },
  { front: "<b>MOCA</b>", back: "<b>M</b>inimum <b>O</b>bstacle <b>C</b>learance<br>(1000’)" },
  { front: "<b>MORA</b>", back: "<b>M</b>inimum <b>O</b>ff <b>R</b>oute <b>A</b>ltitude" },
  { front: "<b>MSA</b>", back: "<b>M</b>inimum <b>S</b>afe <b>A</b>ltitude<br>(25nm Red Circle)" },
  { front: "<b>MTOW</b>", back: "<b>M</b>aximum <b>T</b>akeoff <b>W</b>eight" },
  { front: "<b>MZFW</b>", back: "<b>M</b>aximum <b>Z</b>ero <b>F</b>uel <b>W</b>eight" },
  { front: "<b>NOTAM</b>", back: "<b>Not</b>ice to <b>A</b>ir<b>m</b>en" },
  { front: "<b>NDB</b>", back: "<b>N</b>on <b>D</b>irectional <b>B</b>eacon<br>(Usually 2 Letters)" },
  { front: "<b>OAT</b>", back: "<b>O</b>utside <b>A</b>ir <b>T</b>emperature" },
  { front: "<b>PA</b>", back: "<b>P</b>ublic <b>A</b>ddressing System" },
  { front: "<b>PAPI</b>", back: "<b>P</b>recision <b>A</b>pproach <b>P</b>ath <b>I</b>ndicator" },
  { front: "<b>PIC</b>", back: "<b>P</b>ilot <b>i</b>n <b>C</b>ommand" },
  { front: "<b>PGF</b>", back: "<b>P</b>ressure <b>G</b>radient <b>F</b>orce" },
  { front: "<b>P-RNAV</b>", back: "<b>P</b>recision <b>RNAV</b>" },
  { front: "<b>QRH</b>", back: "<b>Q</b>uick <b>R</b>eference <b>H</b>andbook" },
  { front: "<b>QROUTE</b>", back: "<b>Q</b>uebec <b>Rotue</b> - High Altitude RNAV Airway" },
  { front: "<b>RAIL</b>", back: "<b>R</b>unway <b>A</b>lignment <b>I</b>ndicator <b>L</b>ights" },
  { front: "<b>RAIM</b>", back: "<b>R</b>eceiver <b>A</b>utonomous <b>I</b>ntegrity <b>M</b>onitor" },
  { front: "<b>RNP</b>", back: "<b>R</b>equired <b>N</b>avigation <b>P</b>erformance" },
  { front: "<b>RVR</b>", back: "<b>R</b>unway <b>V</b>isual <b>R</b>ange" },
  { front: "<b>RVSM</b>", back: "<b>R</b>educed <b>V</b>ertical <b>S</b>eparation <b>M</b>inimum" },
  { front: "<b>SATCOM</b>", back: "<b>Sat</b>ellite <b>Com</b>munication<br>(ARINC)" },
  { front: "<b>SELCAL</b>", back: "<b>Sel</b>ective <b>Cal</b>ling<br>(ARINC)" },
  { front: "<b>SID</b>", back: "<b>S</b>tandard <b>I</b>nstrument <b>D</b>eparture<br>(On ramp to the sky!)(10-2)" },
  { front: "<b>SIGMET</b>", back: "<b>Sig</b>nificant <b>Met</b>eorological Information" },
  { front: "<b>SLD</b>", back: "<b>S</b>upercooled <b>L</b>arge <b>D</b>roplets" },
  { front: "<b>STAR</b>", back: "<b>S</b>tandard <b>T</b>erminal <b>A</b>rrival <b>R</b>oute<br>(Guide to land!)(10-3)" },
  { front: "<b>STD</b>", back: "<b>S</b>peed, <b>T</b>ime, <b>D</b>ensity" },
  { front: "<b>TACAN</b>", back: "<b>Tac</b>tical <b>A</b>ir <b>N</b>avigation" },
  { front: "<b>TAF</b>", back: "<b>T</b>erminal <b>A</b>erodrome <b>F</b>orecast" },
  { front: "<b>TCH</b>", back: "<b>T</b>hreshold <b>C</b>rossing <b>H</b>eight" },
  { front: "<b>TCAS</b>", back: "<b>T</b>raffic <b>C</b>ollision <b>A</b>voidance <b>S</b>ystem" },
  { front: "<b>TCU</b>", back: "<b>T</b>owering <b>Cu</b>mulonimbus" },
  { front: "<b>TDZL</b>", back: "<b>T</b>ouchdown <b>Z</b>one <b>L</b>ights" },
  { front: "<b>TDZE</b>", back: "<b>T</b>ouchdown <b>Z</b>one <b>E</b>levation" },
  { front: "<b>TeMAC</b>", back: "<b>T</b>railing <b>E</b>dge <b>M</b>ean <b>A</b>erodynamic <b>C</b>hord" },
  { front: "<b>TERPS</b>", back: "United States Standard for Terminal Instrument Procedure" },
  { front: "<b>TMU</b>", back: "<b>T</b>raffic <b>M</b>anagement <b>U</b>nit" },
  { front: "<b>TODA</b>", back: "<b>T</b>akeoff <b>D</b>istance <b>A</b>vailable" },
  { front: "<b>TORA</b>", back: "<b>T</b>ake<b>o</b>ff <b>R</b>un <b>A</b>vailable" },
  { front: "<b>TOW</b>", back: "<b>T</b>ake<b>o</b>ff <b>W</b>eight" },
  { front: "<b>TROUTE</b>", back: "<b>T</b>ango <b>Route</b> - Low Altitude RNAV Airway" },
  { front: "<b>UHF</b>", back: "<b>U</b>ltra <b>H</b>igh <b>F</b>requency<br>(300-3000MHz)" },
  { front: "<b>V<sub>A</sub></b>", back: "Maneuvering Speed<br>(Control AC Safety Speed)" },
  { front: "<b>VA</b>", back: "<b>V</b>olcanic <b>A</b>sh" },
  { front: "<b>V<sub>1</sub></b>", back: "Takeoff Decision Speed<br>(Go or no go speed)" },
  { front: "<b>V<sub>2</sub></b>", back: "Takeoff Safety Speed" },
  { front: "<b>V<sub>REF</sub></b>", back: "Landing <b>Ref</b>erence Speed<br>(Approach Speed)" },
  { front: "<b>V<sub>FTO</sub></b>", back: "<b>F</b>inal <b>T</b>akeoff Speed" },
  { front: "<b>VFR</b>", back: "<b>V</b>isual <b>F</b>light <b>R</b>ules" },
  { front: "<b>VGSI</b>", back: "<b>V</b><b>i</b>sual <b>G</b>lide <b>S</b>lope Indicator" },
  { front: "<b>VHF</b>", back: "<b>V</b>ery <b>H</b>igh <b>F</b>requency<br>(30-300Mhz)" },
  { front: "<b>V<sub>LOF</sub></b>", back: "<b>Lift-off</b> Speed<br>(AC Becomes Airborne)" },
  { front: "<b>V<sub>MCG</sub></b>", back: "<b>M</b>inimum <b>C</b>ontrol <b>G</b>round Speed<br>(Nose Gear Steering)" },
  { front: "<b>V<sub>MCA</sub></b>", back: "<b>M</b>inimum <b>C</b>ontrol <b>A</b>irSpeed<br>(Rudder Steering)" },
  { front: "<b>V<sub>MU</sub></b>", back: "<b>M</b>inimum <b>U</b>nstick Speed<br>(Slowest AC will become airborne)" },
  { front: "<b>VNAV</b>", back: "<b>V</b>ertical <b>Nav</b>igation" },
  { front: "<b>VOR+DME</b>", back: "<b>VOR</b> + <b>DME</b><br>(3 Letters)" },
  { front: "<b>VOR</b>", back: "<b>VHF</b> <b>O</b>mnidirectional <b>R</b>ange<br>(3 Letters)" },
  { front: "<b>VORTAC</b>", back: "<b>VOR</b> + <b>TAC</b>AN<br>(3 Letters)" },
  { front: "<b>V<sub>R</sub></b>", back: "Minimum Pitch <b>R</b>otation Speed" },
  { front: "<b>VROUTE</b>", back: "<b>V</b>ictor <b>Route</b> - Low Altitude Airway with Connecting VOR’s" },
  { front: "<b>V<sub>S</sub></b>", back: "Clean <b>S</b>tall Speed<br>(Flaps Tucked in)" },
  { front: "<b>V<sub>S0</sub></b>", back: "Dirty <b>S</b>tall Speed<br>(Flaps Extended for Landing)" },
  { front: "<b>VSI</b>", back: "<b>V</b>ertical <b>S</b>peed <b>I</b>ndicator" },
  { front: "<b>WAAS</b>", back: "<b>W</b>ide <b>A</b>rea Augmentation <b>S</b>ystem" },
  { front: "<b>WARMATE FC</b>", back: "<ul><li><b>W</b>ind</li><li><b>A</b>ltimeter Setting</li><li><b>R</b>unway Length/Slope</li><li><b>M</b>EL/CDL</li><li><b>A</b>irport Elevation</li><li><b>T</b>emperature</li><li><b>E</b>ngine Bleeds</li><li><b>F</b>laps</li><li><b>C</b>ontaminated Runway</li></ul>" },
  { front: "<b>WP</b>", back: "RNAV <b>W</b>ay<b>p</b>oint" },
  { front: "<b>WX</b>", back: "<b>W</b>eather" },
  { front: "<b>ZFW</b>", back: "<b>Z</b>ero <b>F</b>uel <b>W</b>eight<br>(BOW + Payload)" },
];